2itb.com 2013-07-29

# web hosting provider, domain hosting, create a free web site, free sub domain, free email service

> **Information about our Organisation and Web site**
> 
> Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like 4eit.com . We are based in India . 
> 
> Our principal activities are: 
> 
>   * Domain name registration, 
>   * Domain hosting, Web hosting 
> 

> 
>   
>  Our privacy policy covers 4eit.com and its Web sites:    
> 
> 
> |  Organisation Name:  |  4eit.com   
> ---|---  
> Address:  |  E-3, Industrial Estate   
> City, Zip:  |  Kota , 324007   
> State:  |  Rajasthan   
> Country:  |  India   
> Controller:  |  Prince Jain   
> Web Sites(s):  |  http://www.4eit.com   
> |  http://www.2itb.com   
>   
> Our privacy policy also covers our subsidiary and its Web site:    
> 
> 
> Subsidiary Name:  |  2itb.com   
> ---|---  
> Address:  |  E-3, Industrial Estate,   
> City, Zip:  |  Kota , 324007   
> State:  |  Rajasthan   
> Country:  |  India   
> Controller:  |  Prince Jain   
> Principal activity(ies):  |  Domain name registration,   
> |  Free domain hosting, Free web hosting   
> Web Sites(s):  |  http://www.2itb.com   
>   
> **Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access  
>  **You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data. 
> 
> **The services and links of our Web sites  
>  **Our Web sites enable you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. 
> 
> **Our Web sites also include a link to:**
> 
>   * CommunityArchitect.com 
>   * Everyone.net 
> 

> 
> Such third party Web service providers may collect personal data about our visitors. 
> 
> Automatic Collection of Information  **  
> ** We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 
> 
> We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. 
> 
> **Data Collection and Purpose Specification**
> 
>   * We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 
>   * We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 
> 

>   * To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please  click here 
>   * We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below. 
>   * If we wish to use our visitors' personal data for new purposes, we do not give them the opportunity to consent to those new purposes. 
> 

> 
> **Children's Privacy**   
> 
> 
>   * We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 
>   * We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by: 
>   *  
>   * We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data. 
> 

> 
> **Disclosure and Visitor Choice**
> 
>   * We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations. 
> 

> 
> **Confidentiality / Security**
> 
> We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 
> 
>   * unauthorised access 
>   * improper use or disclosure 
>   * unauthorised modification 
>   * unlawful destruction or accidental loss 
> 

> 
> All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 
> 
> We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 
> 
> **Access to the personal data we may hold about you**
> 
> You can ask us, by: 
> 
>   * sending an email ( ) 
> 

> 
> whether we are keeping personal data about you. 
> 
> Upon request, which you can indicate by: 
> 
>   * visiting this url ( ) 
> 

> 
> We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, almost instantaneously on-line. \- although we may before require proof of your identity -. We will provide the information without any charge. 
> 
> We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 
> 
>   * erased 
>   * rectified or amended 
>   * completed 
> 

> 
> We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. 
> 
> **Privacy Compliance**   
> 
> 
>   * There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation. 
>   * There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation. 
>   * In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are: 
>   * voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure 
> 

> 
> **Self Assessment procedure  
>   **
> 
> Name or designation of the privacy policy person or service  |  webmaster   
> ---|---  
> URL  |   
> Address  |   
> Country  |  India   
>   
> **Privacy Support  
>  ** If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:   
>   
> 
> |  Contact 1   
> ---|---  
> Name/designation :  |  Webmaster   
> Department :  |   
> Address :  |  E-3, Industrial Estate, Kota - 324007, India.   
> Phone Number :  |  +(91-744) 2366276.   
> Fax Number :  |     
> Email address :   
> URL :  |  http://www.4eit.com/contactus.shtml   
>   
> We do not recommend another means by which visitors' concerns may be addressed. 
> 
> **Primary personal data/Business information**   
>   
> 
> x  |  volunteered by each visitor   
> ---|---  
> \-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
> \-  |  collected from private organisations   
>   
>     |  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research &development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
> ---|---|---|---|---|---  
> Name  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Gender  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Address  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> E-mail address  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Phone/Fax number  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> other (describe)  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>     
>   
> |  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
> ---|---|---|---|---|---  
> Employer/organisation  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Job title  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Address  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> E-mail address  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Phone/Fax number  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> other (describe)  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> **Other personal details and profiling data  
>   **
> 
> x  |  volunteered by each visitor   
> ---|---  
> \-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
> \-  |  collected from private organisations   
>     
>   
> |  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
> ---|---|---|---|---|---  
> Personal details  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Physical description  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Family characteristics  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Education and skills  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Life style or personal tastes  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Financial resources  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> other (describe)  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> ** Identifiers    
>   **
> 
> x  |  volunteered by each visitor   
> ---|---  
> \-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
> \-  |  collected from private organisations   
>     
>   
> |  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
> ---|---|---|---|---|---  
> On-line identifiers  | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> x 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Financial identifiers  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> identifiers assigned by Public bodies  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Biometrics identifiers  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> other (describe)  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> **Specific Data**  
>   
> 
> \-  |  volunteered by each visitor   
> ---|---  
> \-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
> \-  |  collected from private organisations   
>     
>   
> |  Technical administration of the Web site  |  Research & development  |  Customer Administration  |  Marketing  |  Trading in personal data   
> ---|---|---|---|---|---  
> Racial or ethnic origin  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Political opinions  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Religious or philosophical beliefs  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Trade union membership  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Health/Medical data  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Sex life  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Police/Justice data such as civil/criminal actions brought by or against the visitor  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> other (describe)  | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \- 
> 
> | 
> 
> \-   
>   
> Section 5: Purposes for which we collect personal data 
> 
> Not offering individuals the opportunity to consent to the use of their personal data for new purposes is inconsistent with the OECD Use Limitation Principle. 
> 
> Section 7: Disclosure and Visitor Choice 
> 
> Not offering individuals the opportunity to consent to the disclosure of their personal data for new purposes is inconsistent with the OECD Use Limitation Principle. 
> 
> * * *
> 
> Privacy Policy as per [ Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development](http://www.oecd.org/)
